<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Aggregated Education Feed</title>
    <link>https://www.thedorey.com/assets/rss/education.xml</link>
    <description>Aggregated Education Feed</description>
    <dc:creator>Derek Leggett</dc:creator>
    <item>
      <title>Secretary DeVos Announces New Funding to Accelerate Education Innovation and Empower Teachers with Professional Development Options</title>
      <link>https://www.ed.gov/news/press-releases/secretary-devos-announces-new-funding-accelerate-education-innovation-and-empower-teachers-professional-development-options-0</link>
      <description>WASHINGTON — U.S. Secretary of Education Betsy DeVos today announced $185 million in new grant funding for 28 school districts, institutions of higher education and nonprofit organizations across the United  States as part of the Education Innovation and Research (EIR) program. These new grant awards will accelerate locally-driven  innovation and improve academic achievement for high-needs students around the  country.</description>
      <source url="https://www.ed.gov/feed">ED News</source>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 15:52:50 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.ed.gov/news/press-releases/secretary-devos-announces-new-funding-accelerate-education-innovation-and-empower-teachers-professional-development-options-0</guid>
      <dc:date>2020-12-15T15:52:50Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Department of Education Announces Joint Final Rule Regarding Equal Treatment of Faith-Based Organizations in Department-Supported Social Service Programs</title>
      <link>https://www.ed.gov/news/press-releases/department-education-announces-joint-final-rule-regarding-equal-treatment-faith-based-organizations-department-supported-social-service-programs</link>
      <description>WASHINGTON – Today, December 14, 2020, the Department of  Education announced a joint final rule with eight other agencies — the  Department of Justice, the Department of Homeland Security, the Department of  Labor, the Department of Health and Human Services, the Department of Housing  and Urban Development, the Department of Agriculture, the Agency for  International Development, and the Department of Veterans Affairs — to  implement President Trump’s Executive Order No. 13831, on the Establishment of  a White House Faith and Opportunity Initiative (May 3, 2018).</description>
      <source url="https://www.ed.gov/feed">ED News</source>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2020 15:08:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.ed.gov/news/press-releases/department-education-announces-joint-final-rule-regarding-equal-treatment-faith-based-organizations-department-supported-social-service-programs</guid>
      <dc:date>2020-12-14T15:08:57Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secretary DeVos Extends Student Loan Forbearance Period Through January 31, 2021, in Response to COVID-19 National Emergency</title>
      <link>https://www.ed.gov/news/press-releases/secretary-devos-extends-student-loan-forbearance-period-through-january-31-2021-response-covid-19-national-emergency</link>
      <description>Secretary DeVos announced the extension of the federal student loan administrative forbearance period, the pause in interest accrual, and the suspension of collections activity through January 31, 2021. Federal student loan borrowers will not be expected to make payments through January of next year.</description>
      <source url="https://www.ed.gov/feed">ED News</source>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2020 22:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.ed.gov/news/press-releases/secretary-devos-extends-student-loan-forbearance-period-through-january-31-2021-response-covid-19-national-emergency</guid>
      <dc:date>2020-12-04T22:37:00Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Department of Education Announces Major Settlement with Temple University for Fox School of Business Falsifying U.S. News &amp; World Report Business School Rankings</title>
      <link>https://www.ed.gov/news/press-releases/us-department-education-announces-major-settlement-temple-university-fox-school-business-falsifying-us-news-world-report-business-school-rankings</link>
      <description>WASHINGTON – U.S. Secretary of Education Betsy DeVos announced today a settlement agreement with Temple University for what the Department alleges are false representations to U.S. News &amp; World Report to bolster the school's ranking in the annual U.S. News college rankings. The Department's investigation probed the alleged submission of false information by Temple's Fox School of Business and Management ("Fox School") to U.S. News &amp; World Report between 2014 and 2018. </description>
      <source url="https://www.ed.gov/feed">ED News</source>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2020 14:59:46 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.ed.gov/news/press-releases/us-department-education-announces-major-settlement-temple-university-fox-school-business-falsifying-us-news-world-report-business-school-rankings</guid>
      <dc:date>2020-12-04T14:59:46Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secretary DeVos Expands on Revamped College Scorecard, Adding Second-year Post Graduation Earnings and Cumulative Loan Data to Help Students Make Informed Choices</title>
      <link>https://www.ed.gov/news/press-releases/secretary-devos-expands-revamped-college-scorecard-adding-second-year-post-graduation-earnings-and-cumulative-loan-data-help-students-make-informed-choices</link>
      <description>WASHINGTON — Delivering on her promise to continually update and improve College Scorecard, U.S. Secretary of Education Betsy DeVos announced today that students can now compare average earnings two years after graduation based on field of study and how much federal student loan debt they can expect to incur, including new information on Parent PLUS loans, based on where they decide to attend school.  </description>
      <source url="https://www.ed.gov/feed">ED News</source>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2020 17:02:35 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.ed.gov/news/press-releases/secretary-devos-expands-revamped-college-scorecard-adding-second-year-post-graduation-earnings-and-cumulative-loan-data-help-students-make-informed-choices</guid>
      <dc:date>2020-12-02T17:02:35Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Department of Education Unveils FSA Partner Connect Portal at Annual Training Conference</title>
      <link>https://www.ed.gov/news/press-releases/us-department-education-unveils-fsa-partner-connect-portal-annual-training-conference</link>
      <description>WASHINGTON — Today, during its virtual 2020 training conference for financial aid professionals, the U.S. Department of Education's (Department) office of Federal Student Aid (FSA) unveiled its latest update to U.S. Secretary of Education Betsy DeVos' Next Gen FSA initiative: the FSA Partner Connect portal. The site, announced by FSA Chief Operating Officer Mark A. Brown, will consolidate the tools that institutions and other partners use onto a single digital platform. </description>
      <source url="https://www.ed.gov/feed">ED News</source>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 18:06:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.ed.gov/news/press-releases/us-department-education-unveils-fsa-partner-connect-portal-annual-training-conference</guid>
      <dc:date>2020-12-01T18:06:25Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prepared Remarks by Secretary DeVos at the Virtual 2020 Federal Student Aid Training Conference</title>
      <link>https://www.ed.gov/news/speeches/prepared-remarks-secretary-devos-virtual-2020-federal-student-aid-training-conference</link>
      <description>Thank you, Mark, for that kind introduction and for your  reliable leadership at FSA.
Thanks, as well, to all of you—thousands of you—who join  us for this year’s conference. It’s exciting to have a record-breaking turnout,  though of course I’d much rather we all be together in person.
The FSA conference this year is like none other.  Navigating the COVID crisis has been challenging—on many fronts. And I’m  inspired by how each of you has risen to the occasion in different ways and how  you continue to put students first.</description>
      <source url="https://www.ed.gov/feed">ED News</source>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 18:05:17 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.ed.gov/news/speeches/prepared-remarks-secretary-devos-virtual-2020-federal-student-aid-training-conference</guid>
      <dc:date>2020-12-01T18:05:17Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secretary DeVos Unveils Interactive Online Portal to Provide Transparency on Use of CARES Act Education Funding by States, Grantees</title>
      <link>https://www.ed.gov/news/press-releases/secretary-devos-unveils-interactive-online-portal-provide-transparency-use-cares-act-education-funding-states-grantees</link>
      <description>WASHINGTON — U.S. Secretary of Education Betsy DeVos announced today a new online portal that clearly shows if states, local educational agencies (LEAs), and institutions of higher education (IHEs) are using the Coronavirus Aid, Relief, and Economic Security (CARES) Act's $31 billion Education Stabilization Fund (ESF) meant to keep learning going for students during the pandemic.</description>
      <source url="https://www.ed.gov/feed">ED News</source>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 18:14:24 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.ed.gov/news/press-releases/secretary-devos-unveils-interactive-online-portal-provide-transparency-use-cares-act-education-funding-states-grantees</guid>
      <dc:date>2020-11-20T18:14:24Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Readout of the Department of Education’s Office for Career Technical and Adult Education ‘Rethink Work Based Learning’ Event with U.S. Education Secretary Betsy DeVos and U.S. Labor Secretary Eugene Scalia</title>
      <link>https://www.ed.gov/news/press-releases/readout-department-educations-office-career-technical-and-adult-education-%E2%80%98rethink-work-based-learning%E2%80%99-event-us-education-secretary-betsy-devos-and-us-labor-secretary-eugene-scalia</link>
      <description>WASHINGTON – Last week, U.S. Secretary of Education  Betsy DeVos convened a diverse group of business, education and workforce  leaders at the Department of Education for a “Rethink Work-Based Learning” Event.  Key Administration officials participating in  the event included  U.S. Secretary of Labor  Eugene Scalia, Assistant Secretary for Career,  Technical, and Adult Education Scott Stump, and Johnny C.</description>
      <source url="https://www.ed.gov/feed">ED News</source>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 16:56:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.ed.gov/news/press-releases/readout-department-educations-office-career-technical-and-adult-education-%E2%80%98rethink-work-based-learning%E2%80%99-event-us-education-secretary-betsy-devos-and-us-labor-secretary-eugene-scalia</guid>
      <dc:date>2020-11-18T16:56:57Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Department of Education Delivers on Trump Administrations STEM Strategy with Historic Investment</title>
      <link>https://www.ed.gov/news/press-releases/us-department-education-delivers-trump-administrations-stem-strategy-historic-investment</link>
      <description>WASHINGTON — The U.S. Department of Education announced today that during the last fiscal year, it has invested $578 million to support high-quality science, technology, engineering, and math (STEM) education for students through its discretionary and research grants. During a STEM education briefing, the Department reported strong progress in implementing the Administration's five-year STEM education strategy, including building on more than $819 million in STEM investments during fiscal years 2018 and 2019.</description>
      <source url="https://www.ed.gov/feed">ED News</source>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 18:56:29 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.ed.gov/news/press-releases/us-department-education-delivers-trump-administrations-stem-strategy-historic-investment</guid>
      <dc:date>2020-11-17T18:56:29Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secretary DeVos Opens Nominations for Second Annual Presidential Cybersecurity Education Award</title>
      <link>https://www.ed.gov/news/press-releases/secretary-devos-opens-nominations-second-annual-presidential-cybersecurity-education-award</link>
      <description>WASHINGTON — U.S. Secretary of Education Betsy DeVos announced today the call for nominations for the Presidential Cybersecurity Education Award, which honors two K-12 educators for excellence in cybersecurity education.
Now in its second year, the Presidential Cybersecurity Education Award is presented annually to one elementary educator and one secondary educator who instill in their students skills, knowledge, and passion for cybersecurity.</description>
      <source url="https://www.ed.gov/feed">ED News</source>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2020 20:56:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.ed.gov/news/press-releases/secretary-devos-opens-nominations-second-annual-presidential-cybersecurity-education-award</guid>
      <dc:date>2020-11-09T20:56:25Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secretary DeVos Releases Statement on The Nation's Report Card Results for 12th Graders</title>
      <link>https://www.ed.gov/news/press-releases/secretary-devos-releases-statement-nations-report-card-results-12th-graders</link>
      <description>U.S. Secretary of Education Betsy DeVos released the following statement on the new reading and mathematics results for 12th grade students on The Nation's Report Card:</description>
      <source url="https://www.ed.gov/feed">ED News</source>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 20:37:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.ed.gov/news/press-releases/secretary-devos-releases-statement-nations-report-card-results-12th-graders</guid>
      <dc:date>2020-10-28T20:37:25Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Department of Education Releases Parent and Family Digital Learning Guide</title>
      <link>https://www.ed.gov/news/press-releases/us-department-education-releases-parent-and-family-digital-learning-guide</link>
      <description>WASHINGTON – The U.S. Department of Education today released a new Parent and Family Digital Learning Guide, a resource to help parents and guardians understand how digital tools can provide tailored learning opportunities, engage students with course materials, encourage creative expression, and enrich the educational experience.</description>
      <source url="https://www.ed.gov/feed">ED News</source>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 20:40:39 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.ed.gov/news/press-releases/us-department-education-releases-parent-and-family-digital-learning-guide</guid>
      <dc:date>2020-10-23T20:40:39Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Department of Education Announces Additional Funding For Earn-and-Learn Opportunities to Prepare Postsecondary Students for Career Success</title>
      <link>https://www.ed.gov/news/press-releases/us-department-education-announces-additional-funding-earn-and-learn-opportunities-prepare-postsecondary-students-career-success</link>
      <description>WASHINGTON – U.S. Secretary of Education Betsy DeVos announced today additional funding for the Federal Work Study (FWS) Experimental Sites, an initiative which expands earn-and-learn opportunities for students by removing barriers to off-campus jobs, allowing students to work more hours, and permitting institutions to pay students for work-based learning  such as apprenticeships, externships, and clinical rotations.</description>
      <source url="https://www.ed.gov/feed">ED News</source>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 20:16:44 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.ed.gov/news/press-releases/us-department-education-announces-additional-funding-earn-and-learn-opportunities-prepare-postsecondary-students-career-success</guid>
      <dc:date>2020-10-21T20:16:44Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Department of Education Uncovers Vast Underreporting of Foreign Gifts and Contracts by Higher Education Institutions</title>
      <link>https://www.ed.gov/news/press-releases/us-department-education-uncovers-vast-underreporting-foreign-gifts-and-contracts-higher-education-institutions</link>
      <description>WASHINGTON – U.S. Secretary of Education Betsy DeVos unveiled a report today detailing the massive failure of many colleges and universities to disclose more than $6.5 billion in funding and resources from  foreign sources including China, Russia, Saudi Arabia, the United Arab  Emirates, and Qatar. Section 117 of the Higher Education Act requires  institutions of higher education to transparently report foreign gifts and contracts, yet over the course of the last year, the Department has uncovered billions in unreported financial ties.</description>
      <source url="https://www.ed.gov/feed">ED News</source>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 20:13:49 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.ed.gov/news/press-releases/us-department-education-uncovers-vast-underreporting-foreign-gifts-and-contracts-higher-education-institutions</guid>
      <dc:date>2020-10-20T20:13:49Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Engagement specialists bridge gaps during pandemic</title>
      <link>https://www.smartbrief.com/branded/3E572E12-3FBC-11D5-AD13-000244141872/547AEA76-71BA-45A1-9D40-FADE84195914</link>
      <description>&lt;div style="clear:both;margin:20px auto;color:#666;"&gt;In response to challenges stemming from the coronavirus pandemic, a Minnesota district has hired two family engagement specia&amp;#160;-&lt;a href="https://www.smartbrief.com/branded/3E572E12-3FBC-11D5-AD13-000244141872/547AEA76-71BA-45A1-9D40-FADE84195914"&gt;More&lt;/a&gt;-&amp;#160;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Teaching and Learning</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2020 13:56:12 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.smartbrief.com/branded/3E572E12-3FBC-11D5-AD13-000244141872/547AEA76-71BA-45A1-9D40-FADE84195914</guid>
      <dc:date>2020-12-24T13:56:12Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>School aims to boost outcomes for Black students</title>
      <link>https://www.smartbrief.com/branded/3E572E12-3FBC-11D5-AD13-000244141872/29352A9E-12CE-4FBF-B497-0A87E17277D5</link>
      <description>&lt;div style="clear:both;margin:20px auto;color:#666;"&gt;A new high-school STEAM academy campus set to open in Denver in the fall is focused on improving education for Black students&amp;#160;-&lt;a href="https://www.smartbrief.com/branded/3E572E12-3FBC-11D5-AD13-000244141872/29352A9E-12CE-4FBF-B497-0A87E17277D5"&gt;More&lt;/a&gt;-&amp;#160;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Transformational Leadership</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2020 13:56:12 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.smartbrief.com/branded/3E572E12-3FBC-11D5-AD13-000244141872/29352A9E-12CE-4FBF-B497-0A87E17277D5</guid>
      <dc:date>2020-12-24T13:56:12Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social media overuse is parents' top health concern</title>
      <link>https://www.smartbrief.com/branded/3E572E12-3FBC-11D5-AD13-000244141872/C42320E3-6F34-4181-8A6C-5828D83FF944</link>
      <description>&lt;div style="clear:both;margin:20px auto;color:#666;"&gt;The effects of students' change in lifestyle during the coronavirus pandemic are among parents' top health concerns, accordin&amp;#160;-&lt;a href="https://www.smartbrief.com/branded/3E572E12-3FBC-11D5-AD13-000244141872/C42320E3-6F34-4181-8A6C-5828D83FF944"&gt;More&lt;/a&gt;-&amp;#160;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Technology in the Classroom</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2020 13:56:12 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.smartbrief.com/branded/3E572E12-3FBC-11D5-AD13-000244141872/C42320E3-6F34-4181-8A6C-5828D83FF944</guid>
      <dc:date>2020-12-24T13:56:12Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teacher: Harder to spot students' mental health issues</title>
      <link>https://www.smartbrief.com/branded/3E572E12-3FBC-11D5-AD13-000244141872/876CE792-BAFB-475A-9CA3-9F70AE1B4F07</link>
      <description>&lt;div style="clear:both;margin:20px auto;color:#666;"&gt;Supporting the mental health of students can be more challenging as they learn in hybrid and virtual environments, says high-&amp;#160;-&lt;a href="https://www.smartbrief.com/branded/3E572E12-3FBC-11D5-AD13-000244141872/876CE792-BAFB-475A-9CA3-9F70AE1B4F07"&gt;More&lt;/a&gt;-&amp;#160;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>The Whole Child</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2020 13:56:12 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.smartbrief.com/branded/3E572E12-3FBC-11D5-AD13-000244141872/876CE792-BAFB-475A-9CA3-9F70AE1B4F07</guid>
      <dc:date>2020-12-24T13:56:12Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Study considers risk of COVID-19 in schools</title>
      <link>https://www.smartbrief.com/branded/3E572E12-3FBC-11D5-AD13-000244141872/DDD841E5-EEBE-47E8-B114-609EB65D9AE2</link>
      <description>&lt;div style="clear:both;margin:20px auto;color:#666;"&gt;If the coronavirus infection rate is controlled, schools -- whether holding in-person or hybrid classes -- do not contribute &amp;#160;-&lt;a href="https://www.smartbrief.com/branded/3E572E12-3FBC-11D5-AD13-000244141872/DDD841E5-EEBE-47E8-B114-609EB65D9AE2"&gt;More&lt;/a&gt;-&amp;#160;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Policy Watch</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2020 13:56:12 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.smartbrief.com/branded/3E572E12-3FBC-11D5-AD13-000244141872/DDD841E5-EEBE-47E8-B114-609EB65D9AE2</guid>
      <dc:date>2020-12-24T13:56:12Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Students push for name change of Ga. high school</title>
      <link>https://www.smartbrief.com/branded/3E572E12-3FBC-11D5-AD13-000244141872/53390050-3E98-46E3-9027-0FB1908AD5AA</link>
      <description>&lt;div style="clear:both;margin:20px auto;color:#666;"&gt;Changing the name of Wheeler High School in Georgia would not erase the experiences of graduates or the past, writes Sydney S&amp;#160;-&lt;a href="https://www.smartbrief.com/branded/3E572E12-3FBC-11D5-AD13-000244141872/53390050-3E98-46E3-9027-0FB1908AD5AA"&gt;More&lt;/a&gt;-&amp;#160;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>Faculty Lounge</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2020 13:56:12 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.smartbrief.com/branded/3E572E12-3FBC-11D5-AD13-000244141872/53390050-3E98-46E3-9027-0FB1908AD5AA</guid>
      <dc:date>2020-12-24T13:56:12Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interrupting Doom Loops: Reflections on Mid-Year Teacher Exits</title>
      <link>https://www.smartbrief.com/branded/3E572E12-3FBC-11D5-AD13-000244141872/A4F71570-F4FD-47AA-9A54-08FBA7F76BBE</link>
      <description>&lt;div style="clear:both;margin:20px auto;color:#666;"&gt;How do we break cycles that send promising young educators out of the profession too early? &amp;#160;-&lt;a href="https://www.smartbrief.com/branded/3E572E12-3FBC-11D5-AD13-000244141872/A4F71570-F4FD-47AA-9A54-08FBA7F76BBE"&gt;More&lt;/a&gt;-&amp;#160;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>New from ASCD</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2020 13:56:12 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.smartbrief.com/branded/3E572E12-3FBC-11D5-AD13-000244141872/A4F71570-F4FD-47AA-9A54-08FBA7F76BBE</guid>
      <dc:date>2020-12-24T13:56:12Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When Netflix Isn't Enough: Fostering True Recovery for Educators</title>
      <link>https://www.smartbrief.com/branded/3E572E12-3FBC-11D5-AD13-000244141872/972CD558-617B-420B-8C64-63A198C9F5A2</link>
      <description>&lt;div style="clear:both;margin:20px auto;color:#666;"&gt;Stressed educators are expected to continuously "recharge for survival" rather than being given opportunities for authentic r&amp;#160;-&lt;a href="https://www.smartbrief.com/branded/3E572E12-3FBC-11D5-AD13-000244141872/972CD558-617B-420B-8C64-63A198C9F5A2"&gt;More&lt;/a&gt;-&amp;#160;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <category>New from ASCD</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2020 13:56:12 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.smartbrief.com/branded/3E572E12-3FBC-11D5-AD13-000244141872/972CD558-617B-420B-8C64-63A198C9F5A2</guid>
      <dc:date>2020-12-24T13:56:12Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SmartBrief will not publish Friday through Jan. 1</title>
      <link>https://www.smartbrief.com/branded/3E572E12-3FBC-11D5-AD13-000244141872/2C1195B2-566F-4FF1-BD3A-7EECDAEB1D10</link>
      <description>&lt;div style="clear:both;margin:20px auto;color:#666;"&gt;In observance of the holiday season, SmartBrief will not publish Friday through Jan. 1. Publication will resume Jan. 4.</description>
      <category>Editor's Note</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2020 13:56:12 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.smartbrief.com/branded/3E572E12-3FBC-11D5-AD13-000244141872/2C1195B2-566F-4FF1-BD3A-7EECDAEB1D10</guid>
      <dc:date>2020-12-24T13:56:12Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How One Teen Handles Anxiety Disorder Through The Pandemic</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2020/12/27/950507371/how-one-teen-handles-anxiety-disorder-through-the-pandemic</link>
      <description>A Michigan teenager shares what it's like to live with an anxiety disorder.</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;A Michigan teenager shares what it's like to live with an anxiety disorder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src='https://media.npr.org/include/images/tracking/npr-rss-pixel.png?story=950507371' /&gt;</content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2020 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2020/12/27/950507371/how-one-teen-handles-anxiety-disorder-through-the-pandemic</guid>
      <dc:date>2020-12-27T13:00:00Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At 3 Top Universities, Black Student Body Presidents Make History</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2020/12/24/949926177/at-3-top-universities-black-student-body-presidents-make-history</link>
      <description>There's a new set of student leaders at some of the country's top universities. And these trailblazers are working to ensure that the quest for racial justice, diversity and inclusion continues.</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;There's a new set of student leaders at some of the country's top universities. And these trailblazers are working to ensure that the quest for racial justice, diversity and inclusion continues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src='https://media.npr.org/include/images/tracking/npr-rss-pixel.png?story=949926177' /&gt;</content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2020 10:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2020/12/24/949926177/at-3-top-universities-black-student-body-presidents-make-history</guid>
      <dc:date>2020-12-24T10:01:00Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Rural America, Fears About The Future Abound As Fewer Students Go To College</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2020/12/24/948030242/in-rural-america-fears-about-the-future-abound-as-fewer-students-go-to-college</link>
      <description>The isolation and uncertainty of the pandemic are driving the dramatic drop in numbers, threatening the already precarious economies of these areas and widening their socioeconomic drift.</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;img src='https://media.npr.org/assets/img/2020/12/18/marcus-coronavirus-rural-1_wide-e2b0ecd7c68a58c2c5f5cf3eae839d83ec0fa999.jpg?s=600' alt='In Bucksport, Maine, the smokestack of a closed mill can be seen in this waterfront view along the Penobscot River.'/&gt;&lt;p&gt;The isolation and uncertainty of the pandemic are driving the dramatic drop in numbers, threatening the already precarious economies of these areas and widening their socioeconomic drift.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;(Image credit: Molly Haley/The Hechinger Report)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src='https://media.npr.org/include/images/tracking/npr-rss-pixel.png?story=948030242' /&gt;</content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2020 10:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2020/12/24/948030242/in-rural-america-fears-about-the-future-abound-as-fewer-students-go-to-college</guid>
      <dc:creator>Jon Marcus</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2020-12-24T10:01:00Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A 'Real Easy' Choice: Biden Introduces Education Pick Miguel Cardona</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/biden-transition-updates/2020/12/23/949593118/a-real-easy-choice-biden-introduces-education-pick-miguel-cardona</link>
      <description>The lifelong educator is the third Latino candidate Biden's put forward for a Cabinet post. On Wednesday, Cardona spoke of the challenges schools have faced this year: "I've lived those challenges."</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;img src='https://media.npr.org/assets/img/2020/12/23/ap_20358618352071_wide-92dd10cf51e6ba73fa5d9809068e4ae3c13831bb.jpg?s=600' alt='Miguel Cardona, President-elect Joe Biden's intended nominee for education secretary, speaks Wednesday in Wilmington, Del.'/&gt;&lt;p&gt;The lifelong educator is the third Latino candidate Biden's put forward for a Cabinet post. On Wednesday, Cardona spoke of the challenges schools have faced this year: "I've lived those challenges."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;(Image credit: Carolyn Kaster/AP)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src='https://media.npr.org/include/images/tracking/npr-rss-pixel.png?story=949593118' /&gt;</content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2020 17:44:17 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/sections/biden-transition-updates/2020/12/23/949593118/a-real-easy-choice-biden-introduces-education-pick-miguel-cardona</guid>
      <dc:creator>Elissa Nadworny</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2020-12-23T17:44:17Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>West Point Professor On Cheating Scandal At The U.S. Military Academy</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2020/12/22/949309336/west-point-professor-on-cheating-scandal-at-the-u-s-military-academy</link>
      <description>NPR's Ari Shapiro talks with Tim Bakken, a law professor at the U.S. Military Academy at West Point, about allegations that more than 70 cadets cheated on a remote exam last spring.</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;NPR's Ari Shapiro talks with Tim Bakken, a law professor at the U.S. Military Academy at West Point, about allegations that more than 70 cadets cheated on a remote exam last spring.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src='https://media.npr.org/include/images/tracking/npr-rss-pixel.png?story=949309336' /&gt;</content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2020 21:05:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2020/12/22/949309336/west-point-professor-on-cheating-scandal-at-the-u-s-military-academy</guid>
      <dc:date>2020-12-22T21:05:00Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden To Pick Miguel Cardona To Be Next Secretary Of Education</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2020/12/22/949309190/biden-picks-miguel-cardona-to-be-next-secretary-of-education</link>
      <description>President-elect Joe Biden plans to nominate Miguel Cardona to be his secretary of education. Cardona will have a lot on his plate, but one of the administration's top priorities is reopening schools.</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;President-elect Joe Biden plans to nominate Miguel Cardona to be his secretary of education. Cardona will have a lot on his plate, but one of the administration's top priorities is reopening schools.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src='https://media.npr.org/include/images/tracking/npr-rss-pixel.png?story=949309190' /&gt;</content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2020 21:05:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2020/12/22/949309190/biden-picks-miguel-cardona-to-be-next-secretary-of-education</guid>
      <dc:creator>Elissa Nadworny</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2020-12-22T21:05:00Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Picks Connecticut Schools Chief Miguel Cardona As Education Secretary</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/biden-transition-updates/2020/12/22/949114642/biden-to-pick-connecticut-schools-chief-miguel-cardona-as-education-secretary</link>
      <description>Cardona is a former teacher and has spent much of the pandemic pushing to reopen schools. President-elect Joe Biden announced his intention to nominate him on Tuesday evening.</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;img src='https://media.npr.org/assets/img/2020/12/22/ap20357561811479_wide-791a3cf99418b5672078641dcfad62ffa93ce083.jpg?s=600' alt='Connecticut Education Commissioner Miguel Cardona, here in January, is President-elect Joe Biden's intended nominee for education secretary.'/&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cardona is a former teacher and has spent much of the pandemic pushing to reopen schools. President-elect Joe Biden announced his intention to nominate him on Tuesday evening.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;(Image credit: Devin Leith-Yessian/Record-Journal via AP)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src='https://media.npr.org/include/images/tracking/npr-rss-pixel.png?story=949114642' /&gt;</content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2020 16:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/sections/biden-transition-updates/2020/12/22/949114642/biden-to-pick-connecticut-schools-chief-miguel-cardona-as-education-secretary</guid>
      <dc:creator>Elissa Nadworny</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2020-12-22T16:08:00Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Than 70 West Point Cadets Accused Of Cheating In Academic Scandal</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2020/12/21/949025580/more-than-70-west-point-cadets-accused-of-cheating-in-academic-scandal</link>
      <description>Instructors at the Army's premier training ground for officers revealed the academic scandal on Monday, saying it's the worst they've seen since 1976. Some called it a national security issue.</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;img src='https://media.npr.org/assets/img/2020/12/21/gettyimages-73752462_wide-6af1ef3f2ff7db1b01f33d607cda84d01f7eb336.jpg?s=600' alt='Army cadets make their way through campus at the U.S. Military Academy in West Point, N.Y., in 2007. This week, over 70 cadets were accused of cheating on an exam — the worst academic scandal since 1976, instructors say.'/&gt;&lt;p&gt;Instructors at the Army's premier training ground for officers revealed the academic scandal on Monday, saying it's the worst they've seen since 1976. Some called it a national security issue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;(Image credit: Don Emmert/AFP via Getty Images)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src='https://media.npr.org/include/images/tracking/npr-rss-pixel.png?story=949025580' /&gt;</content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2020 03:40:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2020/12/21/949025580/more-than-70-west-point-cadets-accused-of-cheating-in-academic-scandal</guid>
      <dc:creator>Vanessa Romo</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2020-12-22T03:40:00Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Despite High Demand For Nurses, Colleges Aren't Keeping Up</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2020/12/21/947496118/despite-high-demand-for-nurses-colleges-arent-keeping-up</link>
      <description>Even before COVID-19, the system wasn't turning out enough nurses to meet the national shortage.</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;img src='https://media.npr.org/assets/img/2020/12/17/krupnick-nursing-shortage-2_wide-8537c166f051625d613933dc198e99f6defa805f.jpg?s=600' alt='Student nurse Gail Powers outside the College Medical Center in Long Beach, Calif.'/&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even before COVID-19, the system wasn't turning out enough nurses to meet the national shortage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;(Image credit: James Bernal/The Hechinger Report)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src='https://media.npr.org/include/images/tracking/npr-rss-pixel.png?story=947496118' /&gt;</content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2020 11:02:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2020/12/21/947496118/despite-high-demand-for-nurses-colleges-arent-keeping-up</guid>
      <dc:creator>Matt Krupnick</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2020-12-21T11:02:27Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At-Risk Teachers Struggle With Returning To In-Person Classes</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2020/12/21/948697843/at-risk-teachers-struggle-with-returning-to-in-person-classes</link>
      <description>Staffing schools for in-person learning hasn't been easy. In North Carolina, the pressure to keep schools open during the coronavirus pandemic has left some teachers without any good options.</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Staffing schools for in-person learning hasn't been easy. In North Carolina, the pressure to keep schools open during the coronavirus pandemic has left some teachers without any good options.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src='https://media.npr.org/include/images/tracking/npr-rss-pixel.png?story=948697843' /&gt;</content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2020 10:02:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2020/12/21/948697843/at-risk-teachers-struggle-with-returning-to-in-person-classes</guid>
      <dc:creator>Liz Schlemmer</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2020-12-21T10:02:00Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congress Poised To Simplify FAFSA, And Help People In Prison Go To College</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2020/12/20/948659930/congress-poised-to-simplify-fafsa-and-help-people-in-prison-go-to-college</link>
      <description>In a bipartisan effort, Congress is close to a deal to simplify the federal financial aid form, or FAFSA, a major policy goal of retiring Republican senator Lamar Alexander.</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;img src='https://media.npr.org/assets/img/2020/12/20/gettyimages-1230039845_wide-75a1270d212d4dccdb421b1acf1ff06edb5a6f2b.jpg?s=600' alt='In a bipartisan effort, Congress is close to a deal to simplify the federal financial aid form, or FAFSA, a major policy goal of retiring Republican senator Lamar Alexander.'/&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a bipartisan effort, Congress is close to a deal to simplify the federal financial aid form, or FAFSA, a major policy goal of retiring Republican senator Lamar Alexander.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;(Image credit: Samuel Corum/Getty Images)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src='https://media.npr.org/include/images/tracking/npr-rss-pixel.png?story=948659930' /&gt;</content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2020 02:07:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2020/12/20/948659930/congress-poised-to-simplify-fafsa-and-help-people-in-prison-go-to-college</guid>
      <dc:creator>Cory Turner</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2020-12-21T02:07:58Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stanford Apologizes After Vaccine Allocation Leaves Out Nearly All Medical Residents</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/coronavirus-live-updates/2020/12/18/948176807/stanford-apologizes-after-vaccine-allocation-leaves-out-nearly-all-medical-resid</link>
      <description>Residents waged a protest on Friday, demanding to know why senior faculty were getting the vaccine before front-line workers who see COVID-19 patients. Stanford has agreed the plan was flawed.</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;img src='https://media.npr.org/assets/img/2020/12/18/20201218_vaccinedemo___dsc4817_wide-bc0b0a109fb39ac626e667bd7bc9073e8f4f3f8a.jpg?s=600' alt='Medical residents and fellows protest the university's vaccine allocation process outside Stanford Hospital on Friday morning in Palo Alto, Calif.'/&gt;&lt;p&gt;Residents waged a protest on Friday, demanding to know why senior faculty were getting the vaccine before front-line workers who see COVID-19 patients. Stanford has agreed the plan was flawed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;(Image credit: Ben Solomon)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src='https://media.npr.org/include/images/tracking/npr-rss-pixel.png?story=948176807' /&gt;</content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Dec 2020 01:04:41 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/sections/coronavirus-live-updates/2020/12/18/948176807/stanford-apologizes-after-vaccine-allocation-leaves-out-nearly-all-medical-resid</guid>
      <dc:creator>Laurel Wamsley</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2020-12-19T01:04:41Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>West Virginia Schools Chief Declares A Snow Day Despite Remote Learning</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2020/12/17/947693860/west-virginia-schools-chief-declares-a-snow-day-despite-remote-learning</link>
      <description>NPR's Ailsa Chang talks with Bondy Shay Gibson, superintendent for Jefferson County Public Schools in West Virginia, about her decision to declare a snow day even though schools are teaching remotely.</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;NPR's Ailsa Chang talks with Bondy Shay Gibson, superintendent for Jefferson County Public Schools in West Virginia, about her decision to declare a snow day even though schools are teaching remotely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src='https://media.npr.org/include/images/tracking/npr-rss-pixel.png?story=947693860' /&gt;</content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2020 21:05:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2020/12/17/947693860/west-virginia-schools-chief-declares-a-snow-day-despite-remote-learning</guid>
      <dc:date>2020-12-17T21:05:00Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Losing A Generation': Fall College Enrollment Plummets For 1st-Year Students</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2020/12/17/925831720/losing-a-generation-fall-college-enrollment-plummets-for-first-year-students</link>
      <description>Researchers say the pandemic is largely to blame for this year's drastic enrollment declines, but college-going has also been on a decade-long downward trend.</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;img src='https://media.npr.org/assets/img/2020/12/17/brian-williams_stafford-tx_017a_wide-85d25868481f66fd413e7477bf748b8a2dd8fd7d.jpg?s=600' alt='Instead of going to college this fall, Brian Williams got a job at a Jimmy John's near his home in Stafford, Texas. He says paying for college was always going to be hard, but it was even harder to justify the expense during a pandemic.'/&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers say the pandemic is largely to blame for this year's drastic enrollment declines, but college-going has also been on a decade-long downward trend.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;(Image credit: Scott Dalton for NPR)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src='https://media.npr.org/include/images/tracking/npr-rss-pixel.png?story=925831720' /&gt;</content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2020 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2020/12/17/925831720/losing-a-generation-fall-college-enrollment-plummets-for-first-year-students</guid>
      <dc:creator>Elissa Nadworny</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2020-12-17T10:00:00Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What It's Like To Apply To College In The Pandemic</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2020/12/16/947261154/what-its-like-to-apply-to-college-in-the-pandemic</link>
      <description>College applications are different this year: no campus tours, no admission exams and fewer extracurriculars to showcase talents. NPR discusses the challenges of college applications in the pandemic.</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;College applications are different this year: no campus tours, no admission exams and fewer extracurriculars to showcase talents. NPR discusses the challenges of college applications in the pandemic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src='https://media.npr.org/include/images/tracking/npr-rss-pixel.png?story=947261154' /&gt;</content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2020 20:56:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.npr.org/2020/12/16/947261154/what-its-like-to-apply-to-college-in-the-pandemic</guid>
      <dc:creator>Ryan Delaney</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2020-12-16T20:56:00Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Connecting Students to the Real-World of Healthcare</title>
      <link>https://blog.discoveryeducation.com/blog/2020/12/27/connecting-students-to-the-real-world-of-healthcare/</link>
      <description>by Joe Sanchez, PhD MBA, Director of R&amp;#38;D Science Engagement at AstraZeneca As kids continue to navigate the new school year, whether in-person or virtually, being aware of overlapping diseases and social realities has become more important than ever. Beyond the ever-present threats posed by the COVID-19 pandemic, there are 6.2 million children living with asthma in</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;img width="230" height="130" src="https://blog.discoveryeducation.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/AZ-Twitter-1200x675-DEX-230x130.png" class="attachment-medium size-medium wp-post-image" alt="" loading="lazy" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" srcset="https://blog.discoveryeducation.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/AZ-Twitter-1200x675-DEX-230x130.png 230w, https://blog.discoveryeducation.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/AZ-Twitter-1200x675-DEX-640x360.png 640w, https://blog.discoveryeducation.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/AZ-Twitter-1200x675-DEX-768x432.png 768w, https://blog.discoveryeducation.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/AZ-Twitter-1200x675-DEX-677x384.png 677w, https://blog.discoveryeducation.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/AZ-Twitter-1200x675-DEX.png 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 230px) 100vw, 230px" /&gt;&lt;div id="header" class="header"&gt;
&lt;div id="header__login" class="header__login"&gt;
&lt;div id="header-region" class="header-region"&gt;
&lt;div class="header__region region region-header"&gt;
&lt;div id="block-menu-menu-header-nav" class="block block-menu first last odd count-1" role="navigation"&gt;
&lt;div class="content"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id="page-wrapper"&gt;
&lt;div id="page"&gt;
&lt;div id="main-wrapper"&gt;
&lt;div id="main" class="clearfix with-navigation"&gt;
&lt;div id="content" class="column"&gt;
&lt;div class="section"&gt;
&lt;div id="node-304226" class="node node-fmr view-mode-fmr_blog node-by-viewer clearfix"&gt;
&lt;h1 id="fmr-title"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 16px;"&gt;by Joe Sanchez, PhD MBA, Director of R&amp;#38;D Science Engagement at AstraZeneca&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;As kids continue to navigate the new school year, whether in-person or virtually, being aware of overlapping diseases and social realities has become more important than ever. Beyond the ever-present threats posed by the COVID-19 pandemic, there are &lt;a href="https://www.aafa.org/asthma-facts/#:~:text=Asthma%20is%20more%20common%20in%20children%20than%20adults.&amp;#38;text=Asthma%20is%20more%20common%20in%20boys%20than%20girls.&amp;#38;text=Currently%2C%20there%20are%20about%206.2,age%20of%2018%20with%20asthma.&amp;#38;text=In%202017%2C%201%20in%2012%20children%20had%20asthma." target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;6.2 million children&lt;/a&gt; living with asthma in the United States alone. For these children, respiratory diseases like COVID-19 pose additional threats to a healthy life, and complications are everywhere – even from cleaning products, &lt;a href="https://www.thelancet.com/journals/lanres/article/PIIS2213-2600(20)30353-2/fulltext" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;research&lt;/a&gt; finds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Added to the mix are racial disparities related to respiratory illness. &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/coronavirus/2019-ncov/covid-data/investigations-discovery/hospitalization-death-by-race-ethnicity.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Research from the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention&lt;/a&gt; shows cases are up to 2.8x higher among people of color and that Black people, specifically, are &lt;a href="https://www.aafa.org/asthma-facts/#:~:text=Asthma%20is%20more%20common%20in%20children%20than%20adults.&amp;#38;text=Asthma%20is%20more%20common%20in%20boys%20than%20girls.&amp;#38;text=Currently%2C%20there%20are%20about%206.2,age%20of%2018%20with%20asthma.&amp;#38;text=In%202017%2C%201%20in%2012%20children%20had%20asthma." target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;3x more likely&lt;/a&gt; to die of an asthma attack.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Opportunities exist to empower students to make health and science personal by connecting to these realities in the classroom.  Real-world, no-cost resources include those from Generation Health – a program from AstraZeneca, Learning Undefeated, and Discovery Education. This platform makes the connection between students’ health and the science behind the prevention and treatment of disease with standards-aligned experiential learning resources for students in grades 6-8.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Students and educators can kick off the conversation about preventative measures and innovative solutions to complicated topics, like asthma and COVID-19, with key resources such as:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.howsciencepowersus.com/education-resources/educator-resources-respiratory" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;ALL NEW “Air Quality and You” Digital Lesson Bundle&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr" role="presentation"&gt;Learn how air quality and noncommunicable diseases, such as asthma, can affect you and the people around us in three 45-minute sessions. Through this digital lesson, students will gain an understanding about how asthma causes symptoms that make breathing more difficult.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr" role="presentation"&gt;Students will also explore how substances in the environment can enter the body and how pollutants can trigger or exacerbate respiratory symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.howsciencepowersus.com/education-resources/educator-resources-respiratory" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Escape the Pandemic Activity&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr" role="presentation"&gt;In less than an hour, guide students (or have them direct their own learning!) to discover how scientists race around the clock to find a cure for a flu pandemic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr" role="presentation"&gt;Through this real-world scenario, students will see how a virus spreads from person-to-person around the world and has the power to affect a very large number of people. By the end, students discover the health risks of influenzas and various ways to stop the spread of disease just in time for the start of flu season.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;These digital lesson bundles are full of research-based resources and content designed to make anywhere learning fun and easy for the teacher and students. With Generation Health content in hand, educators can inspire students to consider STEM careers while learning together about critical healthcare topics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Learn more at &lt;a href="https://www.howsciencepowersus.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;howsciencepowersus.com&lt;/a&gt; and on  the &lt;a href="https://app.discoveryeducation.com/learn/channels/channel/ceefc089-e5a3-4748-a95d-1e66b7f112fd"&gt;Generation Health channel&lt;/a&gt; in Discovery Education &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.discoveryeducation.com/solutions/experience/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Experience&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded>
      <category>Classroom Content</category>
      <category>Education</category>
      <category>Experience</category>
      <category>Generation Health</category>
      <category>Health</category>
      <category>Hear from experts</category>
      <category>Science</category>
      <category>STEM</category>
      <category>Virtual Field Trips</category>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2020 08:46:41 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.discoveryeducation.com/?p=94732</guid>
      <dc:creator>Jacqueline Kavege</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2020-12-27T08:46:41Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prevention Resources to Keep Kids Substance-Free</title>
      <link>https://blog.discoveryeducation.com/blog/2020/12/25/prevention-resources-to-keep-kids-substance-free-2/</link>
      <description>by Helen Gaynor, Director of Educational Programs at Responsibility.org We know kids don’t live in a vacuum and are faced with important decisions each day. That’s why Responsibility.org’s Ask, Listen, Learn: Kids and Alcohol Don’t Mix underage drinking prevention program and Discovery Education teamed up in 2018 to deliver award-winning prevention resources designed to spark conversations about</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;img width="230" height="130" src="https://blog.discoveryeducation.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/resp_blog_10.16-1-230x130.png" class="attachment-medium size-medium wp-post-image" alt="" loading="lazy" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" srcset="https://blog.discoveryeducation.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/resp_blog_10.16-1-230x130.png 230w, https://blog.discoveryeducation.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/resp_blog_10.16-1-640x360.png 640w, https://blog.discoveryeducation.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/resp_blog_10.16-1.png 650w" sizes="(max-width: 230px) 100vw, 230px" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;by Helen Gaynor, Director of Educational Programs at Responsibility.org&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="fmr-associated-content-region"&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;We know kids don’t live in a vacuum and are faced with important decisions each day. That’s why Responsibility.org’s &lt;em&gt;Ask, Listen, Learn: Kids and Alcohol Don’t Mix &lt;/em&gt;underage drinking prevention program and Discovery Education teamed up in 2018 to deliver award-winning prevention resources designed to spark conversations about alcohol, both in schools and at home, to prevent underage drinking. Now, we’re proud to release brand-new content that supports teachers, parents, and students in engaging in even more conversations to keep kids substance-free by addressing how underage cannabis use affects the developing brain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Cannabis legalization is on the rise in many states: only in eight states and federally is the substance still fully illegal. Yet, as marijuana legislation becomes more common, any form of legalization is only for adults 21+. According to recent &lt;a href="https://www.samhsa.gov/marijuana" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;research&lt;/a&gt; by the Substance Abuse and Mental Health Services Administration (SAMHSA), 1-in-6 people who start using the substance before the age of 18 can become addicted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;To help address this issue,&lt;em&gt; Ask, Listen, Learn &lt;/em&gt;in partnership with Discovery Education offers a new suite of science-based, no-cost resources focused on how cannabis affects the developing brain. Designed with the whole child in mind, these new resources focus on how kids interact with society and how society influences their behavior.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Bring this topic into the classroom with these three activities (appropriate for both asynchronous and synchronous learning):&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr" role="presentation"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Marijuana and Adolescent Health&lt;/em&gt; – Delve into the recommendations and reasoning behind minimum age requirements and the role of legalization by having students role-play as elected officials in a debate focused on the importance of health education in schools.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr" role="presentation"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Marijuana and Your Brain&lt;/em&gt; – Separate cannabis facts from fiction by exploring the role of the developing brain’s endocannabinoid system and how its neurotransmitters are affected through creative writing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr" role="presentation"&gt;&lt;em&gt;How and Why to Say “NO”&lt;/em&gt; – Foster student collaboration around the short-term and long-term effects of cannabis on the developing brain with refusal and exit-strategy practice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Educators can help students continue these conversations at home with resources designed specifically for families. As we know, parents are the #1 influence on a kid’s decision to drink – or not to drink – alcohol, so we developed resources to support parents and guardians when having conversations with kids about many risky behaviors:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr" role="presentation"&gt;&lt;em&gt;When it Comes to Teens&lt;/em&gt;: What You Need to Know about Cannabis – Help families engage in meaningful discussions with kids to keep them substance-free and offer strategies to keep the lines of communication open.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Together, let’s equip students in grades 5-7 with the tools to say “YES” to a healthy lifestyle and “NO” to all risky behaviors.  Informed students make better decisions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Access program resources at &lt;a href="https://www.discoverbrainbodybehavior.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;DiscoverBrainBodyBehavior.com&lt;/a&gt; or through &lt;a href="https://www.discoveryeducation.com/solutions/experience/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Discovery Education&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.discoveryeducation.com/solutions/experience/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt; Experience&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;’s &lt;a href="https://app.discoveryeducation.com/learn/channels/channel/5599ab6d-5216-41c4-bc3f-ff5da0490e4c"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Ask, Listen, Learn&lt;/em&gt; channel&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Explore even more content from Responsibility.org’s &lt;a href="https://asklistenlearn.org/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Ask, Listen, Learn: Kids and Alcohol Don’t Mix&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, whose mission is to eliminate underage drinking and keep kids alcohol- and cannabis-free.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content:encoded>
      <category>Ask Listen Learn</category>
      <category>Classroom Content</category>
      <category>Education</category>
      <category>Experience</category>
      <category>Health</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2020 02:00:21 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.discoveryeducation.com/?p=94717</guid>
      <dc:creator>Jacqueline Kavege</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2020-12-25T02:00:21Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tools Connecting High Schoolers to Financial Success</title>
      <link>https://blog.discoveryeducation.com/blog/2020/12/24/tools-connecting-high-schoolers-to-financial-success/</link>
      <description>Research from the U.S. Treasury Department implies that educating students about smart financial decisions is as critical as ever: only 1 out of 6 students currently have the baseline of economic knowledge they need to be successful long-term. Connecting students to financial know-how, including information about financial institutions, provides a means for young people to achieve their dreams. With</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;img width="130" height="130" src="https://blog.discoveryeducation.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/CEP-Image_Card-560x560-Discover-130x130.png" class="attachment-medium size-medium wp-post-image" alt="" loading="lazy" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" srcset="https://blog.discoveryeducation.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/CEP-Image_Card-560x560-Discover-130x130.png 130w, https://blog.discoveryeducation.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/CEP-Image_Card-560x560-Discover-360x360.png 360w, https://blog.discoveryeducation.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/CEP-Image_Card-560x560-Discover-110x110.png 110w, https://blog.discoveryeducation.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/CEP-Image_Card-560x560-Discover-192x192.png 192w, https://blog.discoveryeducation.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/CEP-Image_Card-560x560-Discover-200x200.png 200w, https://blog.discoveryeducation.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/CEP-Image_Card-560x560-Discover.png 560w" sizes="(max-width: 130px) 100vw, 130px" /&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Research from the &lt;a href="https://www.fdic.gov/consumers/assistance/protection/depaccounts/youthsavings/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;U.S. Treasury Department&lt;/a&gt; implies that educating students about smart financial decisions is as critical as ever: only &lt;a href="https://www.pathwaytofinancialsuccess.org/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;1 out of 6 students&lt;/a&gt; currently have the baseline of economic knowledge they need to be successful long-term.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Connecting students to financial know-how, including information about financial institutions, provides a means for young people to achieve their dreams. With no cost resources from&lt;em&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.pathwayinschools.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Pathway to Financial Success in School&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/em&gt;– a program from Discover Financial Services and Discovery Education – educators now have a way to give students the tools they need to succeed financially.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Designed for wherever learning takes place, the all-new self-paced modules for high school students connect the classroom to the real-world in meaningful and accessible ways.  Whether planning for college or other major life decisions, these modules help students construct healthy money habits that last a lifetime.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;In the &lt;strong&gt;Understanding Financial Institutions&lt;/strong&gt; module, high schoolers practice the critical thinking skills needed to decide which bank or credit union is right for them. This module also helps students explore the world of financial institutions to discover how they work and how the online-only environment transforms money management.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Students can then go even deeper in the &lt;strong&gt;Opening New Accounts&lt;/strong&gt; module. In this module students learn the answers to questions such like: What do you need to do before opening a bank account? Which institution meets your needs? How does age impact accounts?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;The &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.pathwayinschools.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Pathway to Financial Success in School&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/em&gt;resources can be integrated into instruction in a variety of ways. No matter how they are used, they will help all students take control of their financial future. Find the dynamic digital content available to educators, students, and families at no cost at &lt;a href="https://www.pathwayinschools.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;pathwaysinschools.com&lt;/a&gt;. For Discovery Education &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.discoveryeducation.com/solutions/experience/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Experience&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; users in both the Financial Literacy channel and the &lt;a href="https://app.discoveryeducation.com/learn/channels/channel/51cbf7ae-75b2-48f9-863a-cd57c9f579b2"&gt;Pathway to Financial Success in School channel&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded>
      <category>Classroom Content</category>
      <category>Education</category>
      <category>Experience</category>
      <category>Financial Literacy</category>
      <category>Pathway to Financial Success</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2020 19:59:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.discoveryeducation.com/?p=94708</guid>
      <dc:creator>Jacqueline Kavege</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2020-12-24T19:59:09Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 Steps to Become a Student-Centered Educator in Any Teaching Environment</title>
      <link>https://blog.discoveryeducation.com/blog/2020/12/22/2-steps-to-become-a-student-centered-educator-in-any-teaching-environment/</link>
      <description>By Saki Hashimoto, Learning Facilitator, TGR Foundation – A Tiger Woods Charity Student engagement, in either the in-person or virtual environment, is critical to learning.  One way to immediately connect with students and heighten engagement is to teach in the student-centered approach. The student-centered approach emphasizes authentic opportunities for students to be creators of information,</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;img width="156" height="130" src="https://blog.discoveryeducation.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/TGR-PD-300x250-1-156x130.gif" class="attachment-medium size-medium wp-post-image" alt="" loading="lazy" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Saki Hashimoto, Learning Facilitator, TGR Foundation – A Tiger Woods Charity&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Student engagement, in either the in-person or virtual environment, is critical to learning.  One way to immediately connect with students and heighten engagement is to teach in the student-centered approach. The student-centered approach emphasizes authentic opportunities for students to be creators of information, not just consumers of information.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Here’s a two-step process to make the student-centered approach come alive in your own teaching, no matter where learning is taking place:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr" role="presentation"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reflect on your teaching style.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Teachers teach in ways that fit state and national standards, but also in ways that they know. After a semester or two of distance or hybrid learning, teachers need time to reflect. Now is the time to ask yourself questions like:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr" role="presentation"&gt;What do I need to be a more effective instructor?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr" role="presentation"&gt;In what ways does my curriculum provide space for students to discover?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr" role="presentation"&gt;What do I want engaged students to look like?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr" role="presentation"&gt;How do I transform my learning environment so that students are active in their learning process?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Take the time you need to sit back and think about these questions and how you would answer them. Be honest with yourself. Then, start to find answers to your ideas with resources designed to support you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol start="2"&gt;
&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr" role="presentation"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Explore professional learning resources that help you bring students back to the center.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Discover new resources to support your efforts. Set aside 30-45 minutes to take advantage of a new no cost &lt;a href="https://tgreduexplore.org/professional-development/bringing-students-back-to-the-center/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;professional development learning module&lt;/a&gt; designed to empower teachers to create a student-centered learning environment. This &lt;a href="https://tgreduexplore.org/professional-development/bringing-students-back-to-the-center/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;module&lt;/a&gt; from TGR EDU: Explore – an educational program from TGR Foundation and Discovery Education – uncovers concrete strategies for improving the students’ learning experiences in a variety of disciplines&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;In the online module, educators find the one-stop tool that helps identify areas of growth in their own practice. Plus, teachers can go even deeper with the in-depth companion guide, chocked full of helpful information like activities, resources, discussion questions, and other resources.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;At the end of the interactive module, educators can:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr" role="presentation"&gt;Distinguish between a teacher-centered and student-centered classroom environment&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr" role="presentation"&gt;Articulate why a student-centered learning environment is beneficial for students&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr" role="presentation"&gt;Identify multiple tools and strategies to implement a student-centered learning environment&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr" role="presentation"&gt;Reflect on the learning environment using a self-assessment rubric&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;The module provides clarity of the intended goals and outcomes of creating a student-centered environment by examining your current learning environment and providing direction for creating opportunities for collaboration, creativity, and engagement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In summary&amp;#8230;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Through a student-centered approach, students become more engaged in learning and receive opportunities to develop critical skills, knowledge, and practices that will help them thrive beyond graduation. Turn to &lt;a href="https://tgreduexplore.org/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;TGR EDU: Explore&lt;/a&gt;’s professional learning resources that deliver teaching strategies focused on connecting all students to success in school and beyond&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded>
      <category>Cross Curricular</category>
      <category>Education</category>
      <category>Experience</category>
      <category>Professional Development</category>
      <category>STEM</category>
      <category>STEM Resources</category>
      <category>TGR EDU:Explore</category>
      <category>Virtual Field Trips</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2020 18:44:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.discoveryeducation.com/?p=94696</guid>
      <dc:creator>Jacqueline Kavege</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2020-12-22T18:44:27Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discover Resources to Support Emotional Resiliency in Teachers and Students with Ready, Set, RISE </title>
      <link>https://blog.discoveryeducation.com/blog/2020/12/21/discover-resources-to-support-emotional-resiliency-in-teachers-and-students-with-ready-set-rise/</link>
      <description>In what has been an unprecedented and challenging year for schools across the U.S., educators now have access to new, no-cost digital content that supports their own and their students’ emotional resiliency from Ready, Set, RISE!, a unique virtual resource from Kaiser Permanente, Alliance for a Healthier Generation (Healthier Generation), and Discovery Education.   Ready, Set,</description>
      <content:encoded>&lt;img width="230" height="120" src="https://blog.discoveryeducation.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/Kaiser-Google-Landscape-1200x628-DEX-230x120.png" class="attachment-medium size-medium wp-post-image" alt="" loading="lazy" style="float:right; margin:0 0 10px 10px;" srcset="https://blog.discoveryeducation.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/Kaiser-Google-Landscape-1200x628-DEX-230x120.png 230w, https://blog.discoveryeducation.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/Kaiser-Google-Landscape-1200x628-DEX-640x335.png 640w, https://blog.discoveryeducation.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/Kaiser-Google-Landscape-1200x628-DEX-768x402.png 768w, https://blog.discoveryeducation.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/Kaiser-Google-Landscape-1200x628-DEX-770x400.png 770w, https://blog.discoveryeducation.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/Kaiser-Google-Landscape-1200x628-DEX.png 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 230px) 100vw, 230px" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-contrast="none"&gt;In what has been an unprecedented and challenging year for schools across the U.S., educators now have access to new, no-cost digital content that supports their own and their students’ emotional resiliency from Ready, Set, RISE!, a unique virtual resource from &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://about.kaiserpermanente.org/our-story/news"&gt;&lt;span data-contrast="none"&gt;Kaiser Permanente&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span data-contrast="none"&gt;, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.healthiergeneration.org/"&gt;&lt;span data-contrast="none"&gt;Alliance for a Healthier Generation &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span data-contrast="none"&gt;(Healthier Generation), and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-contrast="none"&gt;Discovery Education&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-contrast="none"&gt;. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props="{}"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-contrast="none"&gt;Ready, Set, RISE! offers educators on-demand e-learning modules built to highlight the importance of human connection and empathy in schools. The series provides a foundational understanding of trauma-informed educational practices and policies &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-contrast="none"&gt;educators&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-contrast="none"&gt; can use to create more student-centered learning environments for all learners.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-contrast="none"&gt; The goal of the program is to help cultivate trauma-informed educators, ultimately creating a better world for both educators and students.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props="{&amp;#34;335559738&amp;#34;:240,&amp;#34;335559739&amp;#34;:240}"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-contrast="none"&gt;The first module &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-contrast="none"&gt;in the series &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-contrast="none"&gt;focuses on educator self-care in any teaching environment, while the second module offers educators new strategies for helping students neutralize the effects of adversity, societal oppression, and implicit bias. Additional modules, coming in early 2021, will address how to recognize and respond to sign&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-contrast="none"&gt;s&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-contrast="none"&gt; of trauma in schools and explore the science of implementation. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props="{&amp;#34;335559738&amp;#34;:240,&amp;#34;335559739&amp;#34;:240}"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-contrast="none"&gt;Ready, Set, RISE! is the latest addition to the RISE initiative and is a natural extension of Kaiser Permanente’s leadership role in building healthier schools and communities. Developed as part of Kaiser Permanente’s Thriving Schools initiative, RISE works with students, school staff, teachers, districts, and the community to better understand the underlying factors of stress in schools and develop strategies and practices that foster more positive school environments. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props="{&amp;#34;335559738&amp;#34;:240,&amp;#34;335559739&amp;#34;:240}"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-contrast="none"&gt;More than ever before, social-emotional health is foundational to optimal health and learning development for &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-contrast="none"&gt;students&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-contrast="none"&gt; – and especially those who have been hit hardest by the current public health crisis&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-contrast="none"&gt;. Through resources provided as part of this collaboration between&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-contrast="none"&gt; Healthier Generation&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-contrast="none"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-contrast="none"&gt; Kaiser Permanente and Discovery Educatio&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-contrast="none"&gt;n, educators can &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-contrast="none"&gt;build the&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-contrast="none"&gt;ir&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-contrast="none"&gt; resiliency in ways that are critical &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-contrast="none"&gt;developing a stronger learning environment.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props="{&amp;#34;335559738&amp;#34;:240,&amp;#34;335559739&amp;#34;:240}"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-contrast="none"&gt;Learn more about Ready, Set, RISE! and find all the no-cost resources designed for educators at &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.readysetrisemodules.com/"&gt;&lt;span data-contrast="none"&gt;readysetrisemodules.com &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span data-contrast="none"&gt;and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-contrast="none"&gt;in&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-contrast="none"&gt; Discovery Education &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.discoveryeducation.com/programs/experience?utm_source=de_marketing&amp;#38;utm_medium=press_release&amp;#38;utm_campaign=curiosity"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span data-contrast="none"&gt;Experience&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span data-contrast="none"&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props="{}"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded>
      <category>Curriculum experts</category>
      <category>Education</category>
      <category>Hear from experts</category>
      <category>Professional Development</category>
      <category>Ready Set RISE</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2020 11:42:41 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.discoveryeducation.com/?p=94675</guid>
      <dc:creator>Jacqueline Kavege</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2020-12-21T11:42:41Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our 2nd Annual STEM Writing Contest</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2020/12/23/learning/our-2nd-annual-stem-writing-contest.html</link>
      <atom:link xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" href="https://www.nytimes.com/2020/12/23/learning/our-2nd-annual-stem-writing-contest.html" rel="standout" />
      <description>We invite students to choose an issue or question in science, technology, engineering, math or health, then write an engaging 500-word explanation. Contest Dates: Jan. 19-March 2, 2021.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2020 18:02:56 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nytimes.com/2020/12/23/learning/our-2nd-annual-stem-writing-contest.html</guid>
      <dc:creator>The Learning Network</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2020-12-23T18:02:56Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Are the Greatest Songs of All Time?</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2020/12/23/learning/what-are-the-greatest-songs-of-all-time.html</link>
      <atom:link xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" href="https://www.nytimes.com/2020/12/23/learning/what-are-the-greatest-songs-of-all-time.html" rel="standout" />
      <description>What musicians would you include on your “best ever” playlist?</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2020 10:00:11 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nytimes.com/2020/12/23/learning/what-are-the-greatest-songs-of-all-time.html</guid>
      <dc:creator>John Otis</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2020-12-23T10:00:11Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gifts On the Brain</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2020/12/23/learning/gifts-on-the-brain.html</link>
      <atom:link xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" href="https://www.nytimes.com/2020/12/23/learning/gifts-on-the-brain.html" rel="standout" />
      <description>What is this image saying?</description>
      <category domain="">Voice</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2020 08:00:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nytimes.com/2020/12/23/learning/gifts-on-the-brain.html</guid>
      <dc:creator>The Learning Network</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2020-12-23T08:00:02Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Word + Quiz: glut</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2020/12/23/learning/word-quiz-glut.html</link>
      <atom:link xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" href="https://www.nytimes.com/2020/12/23/learning/word-quiz-glut.html" rel="standout" />
      <description>This word has appeared in 186 articles on NYTimes.com in the past year.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2020 07:00:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nytimes.com/2020/12/23/learning/word-quiz-glut.html</guid>
      <dc:creator>The Learning Network</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2020-12-23T07:00:02Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lesson of the Day: ‘‘R’ is for Rohingya: Sesame Street Creates New Muppets for Refugees’</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2020/12/22/learning/lesson-of-the-day-r-is-for-rohingya-sesame-street-creates-new-muppets-for-refugees.html</link>
      <atom:link xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" href="https://www.nytimes.com/2020/12/22/learning/lesson-of-the-day-r-is-for-rohingya-sesame-street-creates-new-muppets-for-refugees.html" rel="standout" />
      <description>In this lesson, students will learn about new Sesame Street characters. Then, they will consider the potential impact of children’s TV shows in different communities.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2020 10:00:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nytimes.com/2020/12/22/learning/lesson-of-the-day-r-is-for-rohingya-sesame-street-creates-new-muppets-for-refugees.html</guid>
      <dc:creator>Nicole Daniels</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2020-12-22T10:00:05Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What New Flavor Ideas Do You Have for Your Favorite Foods?</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2020/12/22/learning/what-new-flavor-ideas-do-you-have-for-your-favorite-foods.html</link>
      <atom:link xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" href="https://www.nytimes.com/2020/12/22/learning/what-new-flavor-ideas-do-you-have-for-your-favorite-foods.html" rel="standout" />
      <description>How do you feel about novelty Oreo flavors like Key Lime Pie, Wasabi and Peeps?</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2020 10:00:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nytimes.com/2020/12/22/learning/what-new-flavor-ideas-do-you-have-for-your-favorite-foods.html</guid>
      <dc:creator>Callie Holtermann</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2020-12-22T10:00:04Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lonely Dining</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2020/12/22/learning/lonely-dining.html</link>
      <atom:link xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" href="https://www.nytimes.com/2020/12/22/learning/lonely-dining.html" rel="standout" />
      <description>Do you miss going out to restaurants?</description>
      <category domain="">Voice</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2020 08:00:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nytimes.com/2020/12/22/learning/lonely-dining.html</guid>
      <dc:creator>The Learning Network</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2020-12-22T08:00:02Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Word + Quiz: factitious</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2020/12/22/learning/word-quiz-factitious.html</link>
      <atom:link xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" href="https://www.nytimes.com/2020/12/22/learning/word-quiz-factitious.html" rel="standout" />
      <description>This word has appeared in one article on NYTimes.com in the past year.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2020 07:00:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nytimes.com/2020/12/22/learning/word-quiz-factitious.html</guid>
      <dc:creator>The Learning Network</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2020-12-22T07:00:02Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Word + Quiz: doctrinaire</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2020/12/21/learning/word-quiz-doctrinaire.html</link>
      <atom:link xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" href="https://www.nytimes.com/2020/12/21/learning/word-quiz-doctrinaire.html" rel="standout" />
      <description>This word has appeared in 19 articles on NYTimes.com in the past year.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2020 07:00:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nytimes.com/2020/12/21/learning/word-quiz-doctrinaire.html</guid>
      <dc:creator>The Learning Network</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2020-12-21T07:00:02Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lesson of the Day: ‘U.S. and States Say Facebook Illegally Crushed Competition’</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2020/12/20/learning/lesson-of-the-day-us-and-states-say-facebook-illegally-crushed-competition.html</link>
      <atom:link xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" href="https://www.nytimes.com/2020/12/20/learning/lesson-of-the-day-us-and-states-say-facebook-illegally-crushed-competition.html" rel="standout" />
      <description>In this lesson, students will learn why U.S. regulators are seeking to break up the social networking giant — and consider what this means for us and Big Tech.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2020 18:14:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nytimes.com/2020/12/20/learning/lesson-of-the-day-us-and-states-say-facebook-illegally-crushed-competition.html</guid>
      <dc:creator>Jeremy Engle</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>2020-12-20T18:14:59Z</dc:date>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
