<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Aggregated PC_video_games Feed</title>
    <link>https://www.thedorey.com/assets/rss/PC_video_games.xml</link>
    <description>Aggregated PC_video_games Feed</description>
    <dc:creator>Derek Leggett</dc:creator>
    <item>
      <title>Yaga</title>
      <link>https://www.metacritic.com/game/pc/yaga</link>
      <description>Smash, clobber and bash the murderous legends of Slavic mythology in this darkly funny action role-playing game that changes every time you play. Play as Ivan, a one-handed blacksmith with incredibly bad luck, who must take on the impossible tasks given to him by the tzar.&lt;p&gt;Publisher: Versus Evil&lt;p&gt;Release Date: Jan 12, 2021</description>
      <category>Games, Movies, Tv, Music</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.metacritic.com/game/pc/yaga</guid>
      <dc:date>2021-01-12T08:00:00Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airborne Kingdom</title>
      <link>https://www.metacritic.com/game/pc/airborne-kingdom</link>
      <description>Airborne Kingdom — the sky city builder. Grow your unique town among the clouds, and fly it across a wide-open landscape. Explore the skies to restore serenity to the world below.&lt;p&gt;Publisher: The Wandering Band LLC&lt;p&gt;Release Date: Dec 17, 2020</description>
      <category>Games, Movies, Tv, Music</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2020 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.metacritic.com/game/pc/airborne-kingdom</guid>
      <dc:date>2020-12-17T08:00:00Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alba: a Wildlife Adventure</title>
      <link>https://www.metacritic.com/game/pc/alba-a-wildlife-adventure</link>
      <description>Even the smallest person can make a big difference. Join Alba, as she sets out to save her beautiful island and its wildlife. And possibly start a revolution. &lt;p&gt;Publisher: ustwo&lt;p&gt;Release Date: Dec 11, 2020</description>
      <category>Games, Movies, Tv, Music</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.metacritic.com/game/pc/alba-a-wildlife-adventure</guid>
      <dc:date>2020-12-11T08:00:00Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shady Part of Me</title>
      <link>https://www.metacritic.com/game/pc/shady-part-of-me</link>
      <description>Overcome emotional struggles across a touching narrative filled with twists and surprises. Embark on a dream-like journey, with breathtaking artistic direction and the enthralling voice of Hannah Murray (Game of Thrones, Skins).&lt;p&gt;Publisher: Focus Home Interactive&lt;p&gt;Release Date: Dec 10, 2020</description>
      <category>Games, Movies, Tv, Music</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 00:00:01 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.metacritic.com/game/pc/shady-part-of-me</guid>
      <dc:date>2020-12-11T00:00:01Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cyberpunk 2077</title>
      <link>https://www.metacritic.com/game/pc/cyberpunk-2077</link>
      <description>Cyberpunk 2077 is an open-world, action-adventure story set in Night City, a megalopolis obsessed with power, glamour and body modification. Assume the role of V, a mercenary outlaw going after a one-of-a-kind implant that is the key to immortality. You can customize your character’s cyberware, skillset and playstyle, and explore a vast city where the choices you make shape the story and the world around you. Become a cyberpunk, an urban mercenary equipped with cybernetic enhancements and build your legend on the streets of Night City. Take the riskiest job of your life and go after a prototype implant that is the key to immortality.&lt;p&gt;Publisher: Warner Bros. Interactive Entertainment&lt;p&gt;Release Date: Dec 10, 2020</description>
      <category>Games, Movies, Tv, Music</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.metacritic.com/game/pc/cyberpunk-2077</guid>
      <dc:date>2020-12-10T08:00:00Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Medal of Honor: Above and Beyond</title>
      <link>https://www.metacritic.com/game/pc/medal-of-honor-above-and-beyond</link>
      <description>Medal of Honor: Above and Beyond is an action-packed and incredibly immersive VR experience set in World War II, where you step into the boots of an agent of the Office of Strategic Services (OSS) in war torn Europe. A deep single-player campaign takes you through historic events on land, air, and sea, sabotaging Nazi bases, subverting enemy plans, aiding the French Resistance, and much, much more. With the Oculus Rift, we’re bringing players into the Medal of Honor series in an entirely new way, with an experience that transports you back to Europe in the 1940s. It’s the closest thing to a time machine you’ll ever see.&lt;p&gt;Publisher: Electronic Arts&lt;p&gt;Release Date: Dec 10, 2020</description>
      <category>Games, Movies, Tv, Music</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.metacritic.com/game/pc/medal-of-honor-above-and-beyond</guid>
      <dc:date>2020-12-10T08:00:00Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orwell's Animal Farm</title>
      <link>https://www.metacritic.com/game/pc/orwells-animal-farm</link>
      <description>Orwell’s Animal Farm is an adventure game where all animals are equal, but some animals are more equal than others. Immerse yourself in George Orwell's story of absolute power and corruption and follow the ups and downs of Animalism.
&lt;p&gt;Publisher: The Dairymen&lt;p&gt;Release Date: Dec 10, 2020</description>
      <category>Games, Movies, Tv, Music</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.metacritic.com/game/pc/orwells-animal-farm</guid>
      <dc:date>2020-12-10T08:00:00Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unto The End</title>
      <link>https://www.metacritic.com/game/pc/unto-the-end</link>
      <description>Unto The End is a challenging combat adventure game in the style of a cinematic platformer. The story is simple: get home to your family. Master read-react combat in intense sword fights. Spot opportunities to trade and use items. An adventure told through your actions, how will you make it home? &lt;p&gt;Publisher: Big Sugar Films&lt;p&gt;Release Date: Dec 09, 2020</description>
      <category>Games, Movies, Tv, Music</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.metacritic.com/game/pc/unto-the-end</guid>
      <dc:date>2020-12-09T08:00:00Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of the Sea</title>
      <link>https://www.metacritic.com/game/pc/call-of-the-sea</link>
      <description>A weird tale of otherworldly mystery. Call of the Sea is a first-person adventure puzzle game set in the 1930s that tells the story of Norah, a woman on the trail of her missing husband's expedition. The search takes place on a strange but beautiful island in the South Pacific, filled with secrets waiting to be unearthed. It is an otherworldly tale of mystery, adventure, and self-discovery.&lt;p&gt;Publisher: Raw Fury&lt;p&gt;Release Date: Dec 08, 2020</description>
      <category>Games, Movies, Tv, Music</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.metacritic.com/game/pc/call-of-the-sea</guid>
      <dc:date>2020-12-08T08:00:00Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drawn to Life: Two Realms</title>
      <link>https://www.metacritic.com/game/pc/drawn-to-life-two-realms</link>
      <description>The quirky Raposa and your drawn hero return in Drawn to Life: Two Realms, the next installment in the beloved franchise! Uncover the mystery of the Shadow and save Mike and his friends.
&lt;p&gt;Publisher: 505 Games&lt;p&gt;Release Date: Dec 07, 2020</description>
      <category>Games, Movies, Tv, Music</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.metacritic.com/game/pc/drawn-to-life-two-realms</guid>
      <dc:date>2020-12-07T08:00:00Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suzerain</title>
      <link>https://www.metacritic.com/game/pc/suzerain</link>
      <description>As President Rayne, lead Sordland into ruin or repair during your first term in this text-based role-playing game. Navigate a political drama driven by conversations with your cabinet members and other significant figures. Beware or embrace corruption; shirk or uphold ideals. How will you lead?&lt;p&gt;Publisher: Fellow Traveller&lt;p&gt;Release Date: Dec 04, 2020</description>
      <category>Games, Movies, Tv, Music</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2020 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.metacritic.com/game/pc/suzerain</guid>
      <dc:date>2020-12-04T08:00:00Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALTDEUS: Beyond Chronos</title>
      <link>https://www.metacritic.com/game/pc/altdeus-beyond-chronos</link>
      <description>Enter the latest installment in the Chronos Series.
Become Lieutenant Chloe, pilot of the massive battle robot Makhia as you face off against the Meteoras, colossal enemies of humanity in a story that takes place 200 years in the future.

Make choices and decisions with the guidance of the Decision Support System.
Pilot the 400-meter-tall Makhia in blood-pumping action sequences.
Be amazed by the concerts of an electronic idol.

The future awaits beyond your screen.&lt;p&gt;Publisher: MyDearest&lt;p&gt;Release Date: Dec 04, 2020</description>
      <category>Games, Movies, Tv, Music</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2020 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.metacritic.com/game/pc/altdeus-beyond-chronos</guid>
      <dc:date>2020-12-04T08:00:00Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>El Hijo - A Wild West Tale</title>
      <link>https://www.metacritic.com/game/pc/el-hijo---a-wild-west-tale</link>
      <description>El Hijo is an exciting spaghetti-western stealth game, in which you guide a 6-year-old boy on his quest to find his mother.
&lt;p&gt;Publisher: HandyGames&lt;p&gt;Release Date: Dec 03, 2020</description>
      <category>Games, Movies, Tv, Music</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2020 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.metacritic.com/game/pc/el-hijo---a-wild-west-tale</guid>
      <dc:date>2020-12-03T08:00:00Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PHOGS!</title>
      <link>https://www.metacritic.com/game/pc/phogs!</link>
      <description>In PHOGS! you play as a duo of dogs on a captivating, puzzle-filled adventure. Linked by a stretchy belly, you’ll need to bark, bite and bounce your way through obstacles set across the themed worlds of Food, Sleep and Play, in co-op or single-player.
&lt;p&gt;Publisher: Coatsink Software&lt;p&gt;Release Date: Dec 03, 2020</description>
      <category>Games, Movies, Tv, Music</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2020 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.metacritic.com/game/pc/phogs!</guid>
      <dc:date>2020-12-03T08:00:00Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Haven</title>
      <link>https://www.metacritic.com/game/pc/haven</link>
      <description>Does love truly conquer all? Two lovers gave up everything, left their entire lives behind, and escaped to a lost planet to be together. Play these lovers, Yu and Kay, at the same time as they settle into an unknown and eerie world. Explore the planet searching for parts and material to fix their ship and make it a cosy home. Enjoy life together as a relatable couple cooking meals, crafting, collecting resources and engaging in meaningful conversations. Fight against those trying to tear them apart by synchroniSing their actions in combat, finding the perfect timing and rhythm, while controlling both characters simultaneously. Glide through the mysterious landscape, explore a fragmented world and fight against what’s trying to tear them apart in this RPG adventure about love, rebellion, and freedom.&lt;p&gt;Publisher: The Game Bakers&lt;p&gt;Release Date: Dec 03, 2020</description>
      <category>Games, Movies, Tv, Music</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2020 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.metacritic.com/game/pc/haven</guid>
      <dc:date>2020-12-03T08:00:00Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Per Aspera</title>
      <link>https://www.metacritic.com/game/pc/per-aspera</link>
      <description>Experience city-building as never before — Overcome near-impossible odds to terraform Mars, cultivate the red-planet’s hidden resources, and unravel the past mysteries of those who’ve attempted the unbelievable feat. Humanity's future rests on your shoulders. &lt;p&gt;Publisher: Raw Fury&lt;p&gt;Release Date: Dec 03, 2020</description>
      <category>Games, Movies, Tv, Music</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2020 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.metacritic.com/game/pc/per-aspera</guid>
      <dc:date>2020-12-03T08:00:00Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Immortals: Fenyx Rising</title>
      <link>https://www.metacritic.com/game/pc/immortals-fenyx-rising</link>
      <description>[Formerly titled 'Gods &amp; Monsters'] Play as Fenyx, a new winged demigod, on a quest to save the Greek gods and their home from a dark curse. Take on mythological beasts, master the legendary powers of the gods, and defeat Typhon, the deadliest Titan in Greek mythology, in an epic fight for the ages.&lt;p&gt;Publisher: Ubisoft&lt;p&gt;Release Date: Dec 03, 2020</description>
      <category>Games, Movies, Tv, Music</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2020 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.metacritic.com/game/pc/immortals-fenyx-rising</guid>
      <dc:date>2020-12-03T08:00:00Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Morbid: The Seven Acolytes</title>
      <link>https://www.metacritic.com/game/pc/morbid-the-seven-acolytes</link>
      <description>Morbid: The Seven Acolytes is a Horrorpunk Action RPG filled with Lovecraftian horrors and Cronenbergian gore.&lt;p&gt;Publisher: Merge Games&lt;p&gt;Release Date: Dec 03, 2020</description>
      <category>Games, Movies, Tv, Music</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2020 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.metacritic.com/game/pc/morbid-the-seven-acolytes</guid>
      <dc:date>2020-12-03T08:00:00Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sam &amp; Max Save the World Remastered</title>
      <link>https://www.metacritic.com/game/pc/sam-max-save-the-world-remastered</link>
      <description>The Freelance Police are back in a remastered version of their first season of episodic adventure games, lovingly updated by a small group of the original developers with the blessing of Sam &amp; Max creator Steve Purcell.
&lt;p&gt;Publisher: Skunkape Games&lt;p&gt;Release Date: Dec 02, 2020</description>
      <category>Games, Movies, Tv, Music</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2020 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.metacritic.com/game/pc/sam-max-save-the-world-remastered</guid>
      <dc:date>2020-12-02T08:00:00Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Twin Mirror</title>
      <link>https://www.metacritic.com/game/pc/twin-mirror</link>
      <description>Sam, a 33-year old man recovering from a recent break-up, returns to his hometown Basswood, West Virginia, for the funeral of his best friend. Understandably depressed and bitter, he feels completely out of sorts and out of place... But when he wakes up in his hotel room with a bloody shirt and no memory of his whereabouts the previous night, he embarks on a twisted investigation to find the truth.

FEATURES:

* Play a Thrilling Investigation -- Recall your memories and find the truth by exploring the dark undertones of a small town in West Virginia.

* Embark on a Compelling Emotional Journey -- Sam's quest is also one of redemption in his journey to find himself again and heal his wounded heart.

* Direct Sam's Fate -- Your choices and values decide Sam's place in life as you shape his relationships with the Basswood's inhabitants.&lt;p&gt;Publisher: Bandai Namco Games&lt;p&gt;Release Date: Dec 01, 2020</description>
      <category>Games, Movies, Tv, Music</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.metacritic.com/game/pc/twin-mirror</guid>
      <dc:date>2020-12-01T08:00:00Z</dc:date>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
